{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"2130","name":"White Castle #38","address":"20409 James Couzens","zipcode":"48235","owner":"White Castle System, Inc.","licenseNumber":"040282","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"365.0","coords":"-83.20073,42.44187","geojson":{"id":"2130","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.200725161,42.441874012]},"properties":{"name":"White Castle #38","owner":"White Castle System, Inc.","address":"20409 James Couzens","zipcode":"48235","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":null,"license_number":"040282","establishmentid":"2130","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"365.0","most_recent_license_date":"5/4/2018"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"3199","name":"Detroit Fish & Shrimp III","address":"20030 James Couzens","zipcode":"48235"},{"establishmentid":"2037","name":"Michigan Technical Academy","address":"19940 Mansfield Ave","zipcode":"48235"},{"establishmentid":"51622825","name":"Pembroke Academy","address":"19940 Mansfield St","zipcode":"48235"},{"establishmentid":"4286","name":"Jalen Rose Leadership Acadamy","address":"15000 Trojan St","zipcode":"48235"},{"establishmentid":"1118","name":"Bow Elementary School","address":"19801 Prevost Ave","zipcode":"48235"},{"establishmentid":"2776","name":"Nu Wave Fish & Chicken","address":"15030 E Eight Mile Rd","zipcode":"48205"},{"establishmentid":"5116","name":"Subway","address":"15000 E Eight Mile Rd","zipcode":"48205"},{"establishmentid":"4915","name":"The Jamaican Pot","address":"14615 W Eight Mile Rd","zipcode":"48235"},{"establishmentid":"1991","name":"Mama's, Inc.","address":"14620 E Eight Mile Rd","zipcode":"48205"},{"establishmentid":"5286","name":"Rinor LLC / Mama's","address":"14620 E Eight Mile Rd","zipcode":"48205"},{"establishmentid":"1475","name":"Burger King ","address":"15500 W Seven Mile Rd","zipcode":"48235"},{"establishmentid":"1179","name":"Nicky D's Coney Island","address":"15447 W Seven Mile Rd","zipcode":"48235"},{"establishmentid":"5009","name":"Uncle Big John's Fresh Fish Mkt.","address":"15834 W Seven Mile Rd","zipcode":"48235"},{"establishmentid":"4414","name":"Saucebar","address":"15838 W Seven Mile Rd","zipcode":"48235"},{"establishmentid":"4998","name":"Encore Lounge and Grill","address":"15407 W Seven Mile Rd","zipcode":"48235"},{"establishmentid":"3537","name":"Fat Boyz Steak and Chicken","address":"15917 W Seven Mile Rd","zipcode":"48235"},{"establishmentid":"4839","name":"Asian Corned Beef","address":"14820 Seven Mile Rd W","zipcode":"48235"},{"establishmentid":"4974","name":"Motor City Sweet Shop","address":"16311 W Seven Mile Rd","zipcode":"48235"},{"establishmentid":"5157","name":"44 Burrito","address":"14015 W Eight Mile Rd","zipcode":"48235"},{"establishmentid":"5221","name":"Captain Jay's #119","address":"14420 Seven Mile Rd W","zipcode":"48235"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"44057","inspectionDate":"2018-11-08T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-602.11","violationDescription":"(A) Equipment FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned:     \r\n  (1) Except as specified in ¶ (B) of this section, before each use with a different   type of raw animal FOOD such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, or POULTRY; (P)   \r\n  (2) Each time there is a change from working with raw FOODS to working with   READY-TO-EAT FOODS; (P)   \r\n  (3) Between uses with raw fruits and vegetables and with POTENTIALLY   HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD);   (P)   \r\n  (4) Before using or storing a FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING   DEVICE; (P) and   \r\n  (5) At any time during the operation when contamination may have occurred. (P)\r\n(B) Subparagraph (A)(1) of this section does not apply if the FOOD-CONTACT SURFACE or UTENSIL is in contact with a succession of different raw animal FOODS each requiring a higher cooking temperature as specified under § 3-401.11 than the previous FOOD, such as preparing raw FISH followed by cutting raw poultry on the same cutting board.   \r\n(C) Except as specified in ¶ (D) of this section, if used with POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD), EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be cleaned throughout the day at least every 4 hours. (P)   \r\n(D) Except when dry cleaning methods are used as specified under § 4-603.11, surfaces of UTENSILS and EQUIPMENT contacting FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be cleaned:     \r\n  (1)   At any time when contamination may have occurred;\r\n  (2)   At least every 24 hours for iced tea dispensers and CONSUMER self-service UTENSILS such as tongs, scoops, or ladles;\r\n  (3) Before restocking CONSUMER self-service EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS such as condiment dispensers and display containers; and\r\n  (4) In EQUIPMENT such as ice bins and BEVERAGE dispensing nozzles and   enclosed components of EQUIPMENT such as ice makers, cooking oil storage   tanks and distribution lines, BEVERAGE and syrup dispensing lines or tubes,   coffee bean grinders, and water vending EQUIPMENT:\r\n     (a) At a frequency specified by the manufacturer, or\r\n     (b) Absent manufacturer specifications, at a frequency necessary to preclude      accumulation of soil or mold.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s) used for nonpotentially hazardous food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not cleaned when contaminated","subProblem":"","location":"ICE BIN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean properly when contaminated."},{"violationCode":"6-501.111","violationDescription":"The presence of insects, rodents, and other pests shall be controlled to minimize their presence on the PREMISES.  by:\r\n(A) Routinely inspecting incoming shipments of FOOD and supplies; \r\n(B) Routinely inspecting the PREMISES for evidence of pests;\r\n(C) Using methods, if pests are found, such as trapping devices or other means of pest control as specified.(Pf) \r\n(D) Eliminating harborage conditions. \r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Pest(s)","subItem":"gnats","problemDescription":"Present in facility","subProblem":"Without use of trapping devices","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Remove pests from facility."},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"40276","inspectionDate":"2017-10-08T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-703.11","violationDescription":"After being cleaned, EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be SANITIZED  by an approved process.\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Quaternary ammonia solution","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Below 100 ppm","subProblem":"","location":"SANITIZER BUCKETS","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-08T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide correct concentration as stated above."},{"violationCode":"6-501.14","violationDescription":"(A) Intake and exhaust air ducts shall be cleaned and filters changed so they are not a source of contamination by dust, dirt, and other materials. \r\n(B) If vented to the outside, ventilation systems may not create a public health HAZARD or nuisance or unLAWful discharge.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Ventilation system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"VENTILATION HOOD SYSTEM","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean"}]},{"inspectionid":"36488","inspectionDate":"2016-09-16T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"GRILL AREA","subLocation":"At the Food Storage","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-09-16T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"violationCode":"3-304.15","violationDescription":"(A) SINGLE-USE gloves shall be used for one task only and discarded when      damaged, soiled, or when interruptions occur in the operation. (P)\r\n\r\n(B) Slash-resistant and cloth gloves shall be used in direct contact only with FOOD that is subsequently cooked. Gloves used with ready-to-eat foods shall be smooth,   durable and non-absorbant.\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Single-use glove(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Used for multiple purposes","subProblem":"","location":"EMPLOYEE(S)","subLocation":"At the Glove usage","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-09-16T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Gloves shall only be used for one purpose and then disposed."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"COOLERS THROUGHOUT","subLocation":"At the gasket/rubber lining","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/Replace"},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN FREEZER","subLocation":"At the Floor","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"FRYER AREA","subLocation":"At the Grease build up","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"2130"}}